<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Viola Ziwei Song</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/Homepage/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Viola Ziwei Song</description>
    <image>
      <title>Viola Ziwei Song</title>
      <url>https://github.com/songssssss/zwsong.github.io/blob/1996de3e4bd35620d30255395a4f88d1c2270bf4/image.jpg</url>
      <link>https://github.com/songssssss/zwsong.github.io/blob/1996de3e4bd35620d30255395a4f88d1c2270bf4/image.jpg</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.132.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2024 violaziweisong</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 13:20:14 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/Homepage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Homepage/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 13:20:14 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Homepage/projects/</guid>
      <description>Real-Time Query Processing Pipeline for TPC-H Workloads Using Apache Flink Mar 2023 - Aug 2023 View details Github
Designed and implemented a real-time data streaming pipeline using Apache Flink to process continuous updates for TPC-H Query 5, optimizing multi-way joins over acyclic schemas Preprocessed and simulated dynamic data environments with insertions, deletions, and randomized streams, showcasing Flink&amp;rsquo;s capability for handling large-scale analytical workloads Achieved high-throughput real-time query processing, validating results against DuckDB benchmarks and demonstrating scalability across varying dataset sizes VIS Vast Challenge 2022 Mar 2023 - May 2023 View details</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Homepage/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 13:21:10 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Homepage/gallery/</guid>
      <description>New York Boston Introduction content goes here. Los Angeles Content related to Topic A. No.1 Road Trip San Franscisco Content related to Topic B. Inner Mongolian Final thoughts and conclusions. Graduation Ceremony Navigation Links: Resume About Go to Topic B Go to Conclusion </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Homepage/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 13:04:58 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Homepage/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I’m Viola Ziwei Song, a data analyst with nearly three years of experience across diverse industries, including banking, research, and medical science. I recently moved from Hong Kong to Toronto to embark on an exciting new chapter in my career and life in Canada.
I hold a Master’s degree in Big Data Technology from The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, where I specialized in machine learning, data visualization, data analysis, and data engineering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Homepage/list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Homepage/list/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt; Timeline 2024 Event description for 2024.
2023 Event description for 2023.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
